Summary

I'm a 21 year old senior Information Systems major/Graphic Design minor from Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, currently attending Coastal Carolina University. I have over 7 years of experience with programming, and almost just as much with graphic design and web development.

Skills

Proficient in:

HTML

JavaScript

AngularJS

Vue.js

Node.js

Express

ES6/ES2016/Babel

Webpack Gulp

CSS

LESS

SCSS

PHP

Laravel

MongoDB

SQL

Lua

Java

Android Studio

C#

Unity

Experienced in:

Python 2.7

VB.NET

C++

ActionScript 2

Proficient with:

Adobe Master Collection (CC)

Illustrator

Photoshop

InDesign

DreamWeaver

After Effects

Git/Version control

Microsoft Office

Experience

Digital Marketing/Social Media internship at Allen Corporation of America

December 2016 - Present

Digital Communication major at The Academy for the Arts, Science, and Technology

August 2012 - June 2014

Internship at Native Sons: Screenprint and Embroidery

January 2013 - March 2013

Education

Coastal Carolina University - Bachelor of Science in Information Systems with Graphic Design minor

August 2015 - June 2018 (Expected)

Horry Georgetown Technical College - Associate's degree

August 2014 - June 2015

Academy for the Arts, Science, and Technology - Digital Communication major

August 2012 - June 2014

Carolina Forest High School

August 2010 - June 2012

Contact

- http://andrewault.me
- /andyault
- **y** @krazy_nd
- @krazy_nd
- ↑ 102 Clemson Road

Conway, SC 29526

(843) 504-7218